<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.seren" version="0.1.28" name="Seren" provider-name="Nixgates">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1" />
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.5.3"/>
		<import addon="script.module.metahandler" version="1.0.0" />
		<import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.2.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.addon.signals" version="0.0.1"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="seren.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Seren - This Addon is currently in beta. Please be aware there may be bugs present</summary>
		<description lang="en">
		</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<forum></forum>
		<website></website>
		<source></source>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon takes no responsibility for any 3rd party intergration or modification of this software, please ensure your use of this software abides by your local and insterstate laws.</disclaimer>
		<assets>
			<icon>temp-icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>temp-fanart.png</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>
Changelog 0.1.28
Added try except in zfile module to handle file as already provided bytes

Changelog 0.1.27
Added delay to setViewType call
Added setting to disable setting viewTypes with Seren
Removed idle, closeAllDialogs, added closeOkDialog, added closeBusyDialog
Removed busy dialog stalling after failure to find sources

Changelog 0.1.26
Increased keep-alive ticks to prevent pre-scrape occuring to early
Reduced busy dialog occurance on failure to scrape
Fixed provider install issue with zipfiles

Changelog 0.1.25
Fixed setSetting argument naming (Fixes pre-emptive scraping)
Trakt lists sorting now ignores 'The '
Removed title appends to follow more closely to Kodi standards, another method of showing play percentage must be met
Fixed Trakt dates for episode items
Added Studio to metadata
Seren now appends next season to current playlist during playback instead of after
Removed references to now defunct OMNIConnect Addon
Added Re-scrape cm item to episode items
Fixed and optimised list pagination
Trakt Lists now use user slugs to support users with periods in their username
Added ability to direct search through plugin url
Confirmed Trakt list sorting for all types except excluded (popularity, percentage, my rating)
Added support to fail resolve if file ends with .rar
Release titles are now deaccented and encoded with utf-8 to prevent unicode errors
Fixed Ghost providers occuring if a provider was no longer available in a updated version of a provider package.
Fixed TVDB module creating an artwork URL if no artwork is available
Added token refresh lock to the TVDB module to stop instances of the class spawning mass refresh requests
Massively reduced chance Kodi will drop Seren's settings
Fixed Real Debrid post request making a get request after token refresh
Custom Provider module now uses Zfile module to accomodate zipfile module bug on Android devices

		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>
